Name Bodey Royce Baker

Date of Birth 5th October 1984

Citizenship Australian

Email bodey.baker@gmail.com
Phone +82-10-2186-1005
Location Seoul, South Korea

Summary

I am a native English speaker from Australia living in Korea and now I am hoping to get some more experience teaching for a few years.

Since the start of March this year I've been working for Wonderland as the homeroom teacher of the six year olds and loving it. Here I was their main teacher for teaching, solving disputes and recreation. I taught conversation, reading, grammar, science and art.

I have previously taught English in primary schools and junior high schools both following a curriculum and planning my own lessons. At university I tutored and demonstrated for engineering and programming units as well as attending the "Seminars, Tutorials and Laboratories" teaching course. During my time working and studying at university I published three academic papers, presented two at conferences and got the highest mark in our only unit on communication, writing and giving presentations.

I really enjoy teaching and now I would like to expand the teaching skills and experience I currently have.



Experience

Kindergarten Homeroom Teacher

- Planning lessons; teaching students English, art and science; and the general care of kindergarten students.
- Teaching conversation and grammar to Elementary students.

Avionics Software Engineer

- Worked in a professional setting programming and designing software for UAVs.
- Wrote internal documentation and manuals.

Tutor

- Tutored the units:
 - Modelling and Computing Analysis for Engineers
 - Java
- Required ability to explain difficult concepts to students who were struggling.
- Duties: teaching, lab demonstrating and marking.

Undergraduate Engineer

• Presented reports on the analysis of accelerometer data to ensure vehicles met vibration requirements.

Assistant English Teacher

- Taught English to primary and junior high school students.
- Duties: planning lessons; teaching; communicating with students.
- Skills: teaching; public speaking; motivating others; integrating into new cultures.

Research Assistant

• Tested a method to explore the structure of a rock sample from 3D data and visualise the output using a 3D projector.

March 2013 - September 2013

Wonderland Seoul, Korea

July 2010 - July 2012 Cyber Technology Australia

July 2009 - November 2009 University of Western Australia

> May 2009 - June 2010 JRB Engineering Australia

May 2008 - February 2009 W5 Staff Services Japan

August 2007 - January 2008

iVEC at the ARRC Australia

July 2007 - November 2007 University of Western Australia

- Tutored the units:
 - Modelling and Computing Analysis for Engineers
 - Mechatronics Systems
 - Java

Research Assistant

December 2006 - December 2007 Centre for Exploration Targeting University of Western Australia

- Studied how roughness changes with direction across rock surfaces.
- Finished with a talk and poster explaining the results to the public
- Published a paper with an academic journal

Education

Bachelor of Engineering (Mechatronics)

2011: The University of Western Australia

The final year project involved designing, planning, a public talk and a large report on a damage detection system.

Bachelor of Computer Science

2006: The University of Western Australia

This project ended with a conference paper, "Strategy specification for teamwork in robot soccer", being presented in front of other researchers and students. Throughout the project there were many public demonstrations entertaining children and their parents.

Scholarships and Prizes

2007: Top of the Computer Science honours unit "Scientific Communication" **2001:** Institute of Engineers award for attaining a TEE score above 75% in:

Chemistry, Physics, Calculus and Applicable Mathematics.

2000: Olympic Torch Escort Runner

Professional affiliations

2007-2008: Webmaster of Ancestrais Capoeira

2007: President of the UWA Association of Mechatronics Engineers2006: Social Engineer of the UWA Association of Mechatronics Engineers2006: Vice-President of the UWA Computer Science Students' Club

2005: Ordinary Committee Member in the UWA Computer Science Students' Club

Interests

Soccer, Rock Climbing, Acrobatics, Capoeira, Machine Learning, Languages, Snow Boarding, Travelling, Cultures.



The University of Western Australia

In the name of the Senate and by authority of the same

be it known that

Bodey Royce Baker

having fulfilled all the requirements was admitted to the degree of

Bachelor of Engineering (Mechatronics Engineering)

and to all the privileges attached to the same on the date stated hereunder



Vice-Chancellor

Registrar

Date: 20 September 2011



The University of Western Australia

In the name of the Senate and by authority of the same

be it known that

Bodey Royce Baker

having fulfilled all the requirements was admitted to the degree of

Bachelor of Computer Science

with Second Class Honours
(Division A)

and to all the privileges attached to the same on the date stated hereunder



Vice-Chancellor

Registrar

Date: 20 September 2011

10 January 2007

Mr Bodey R. Baker 42 Williams Road NEDLANDS WA 6009 School of Computer Science and Software Engineering

The University of Western Australia 35 Stirling Highway, Crawley WA 6009

Phone + 61 8 6488 2716 Fax + 61 8 6488 1089 Email head@csse.uwa.edu.au

MBDP: M002

CRICOS Provider Code: 00126G

Dear Mr Baker

HIGHEST MARK - CITS7200 SCIENTIFIC COMMUNICATION

On behalf of the staff of the School of Computer Science & Software Engineering, but particularly Dr Lyndon While, I would like to congratulate you on achieving the highest mark in the above unit for 2006.

It is a pleasure for all academics to teach students who achieve such good grades in their subjects and who thus contribute to the intellectual life of the School. I wish you all the best in your future studies.

Yours sincerely

Dr Nick Spadaccini

Nickfpadaccini

Head of School

cc Dr Lyndon While - Unit Coordinator